lovense.com 2019-05-21

# Lovense Sex Toys for Long Distance Love

#### 1. _INFORMATION THAT WE MAY COLLECT_

We may collect different types of personal and other identifiable information based on your use of the Services. Wherever the Company collects Personal Data we make an effort to provide a link to this Privacy Policy. When you create an account, use our website, purchase our products, and otherwise use our Services, we collect the following types of information from you:

#### For our websites

  * Information you provide us 
    * Name
    * Contact information (e.g., email address, phone number)
    * Demographics information (e.g., location)
    * Communications between you and the Company
    * Any other information you provide us
  * Device identifiers 
    * Device details of what you are connecting with
  * Log file information 
    * Geo-location information
    * Number of times you access our Services and the nature of your use
    * Language and identifying information
    * Your web requests
    * How you interact with links or features on the Services
  * Metadata and other technical data associated with any user provided information or content
  * Cookies and similar technologies

#### For our Lovense Remote, Lovense Connect, and Body Chat App

  * Information you provide us (this is to display information to you or your partners) 
    * User content, including Text, Pictures, Audio, and Video messages (the “Content”).
    * Your friends list 
    * Any other information you provide us
  * Device identifiers 
    * Device details of what you are connecting with
    * Operating system information
    * Bluetooth connection and status records
    * The product(s) you have connected to our app
    * Device type, model, and/or manufacturer
    * Data files or similar data structures stored on or associated with your user device
    * Data stored in connection with the device hardware, the device's operating system, and/or other software
    * Data sent to your device by the Company
  * Log file information 
    * The version of our app that you are using
    * Login record
    * App crash details
    * Information automatically reported by your browser each time you make a request to access our web page or app

#### For our Lovense Browser and/or Lovense Extension

  * Information you provide us 
    * User Content
    * Your friends list
    * Any other information you provide us
  * Device identifiers 
    * Device details of what you are connecting with
    * Operating system information
    * Bluetooth connection and status records
    * The product(s) you have connected to our app
    * Device type, model, and/or manufacturer
    * Data files or similar data structures stored on or associated with your user device
    * Data stored in connection with the device hardware, the device's operating system, and/or other software
    * Data sent to your device by the Company
  * Log file information 
    * The version of our app that you are using
    * Login records
    * App crash details
    * Information automatically reported by your browser each time you make a request to access our web page or app
    * Browser type
    * How you interact with links or features on the Services
    * Website you are connecting with
    * The tip commands we send out because of a user-defined tip amount
    * Failed commands sent out and the status of your set up

By voluntarily providing us with Personal Data, you are consenting to our use of it in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you provide Personal Data to the Company, you acknowledge and agree that such Personal Data may be transferred from your current location to the offices and servers of the Company and the authorized third parties referred to herein.

We may also collect: **(i)** Non-Identifiable Data. When you interact with the Company through the Services, we receive and store certain personally non-identifiable information. Such information, which is collected passively using various technologies, cannot presently be used to specifically identify you. The Company may store such information itself or such information may be included in databases owned and maintained by the Company, affiliates, agents or service providers. The Services may use such information and pool it with other information to track, for example, the total number of visitors to our Services, the number of visitors to each page of our Services, and the domain names of our visitors' Internet service providers. It is important to note that no Personal Data is available or used in this process. 

**(ii)** Aggregated Personal Data. In an ongoing effort to better understand and serve the users of the Services, the Company may conduct research on its customer demographics, interests, and behavior based on the Personal Data and other information provided to us. This research may be compiled and analyzed on an aggregate basis, and the Company may share this aggregate data with its affiliates, agents, and business partners. This aggregate information does not identify you personally. The Company may also disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our services to current and prospective business partners and to other third parties for other lawful purposes. 

#### 2. _HOW WE USE YOUR PERSONAL DATA AND OTHER INFORMATION_

The Company uses the Personal Data you provide in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. If you provide Personal Data for a certain reason, we may use the Personal Data in connection with the reason for which it was provided. For instance, if you contact us by email, we will use the Personal Data you provide to answer your question or resolve your problem. Also, if you provide Personal Data in order to obtain access to the Services, we will use your Personal Data to provide you with access to such services and to monitor your use of such services. The Company may also use your Personal Data and other personally non-identifiable information collected through the Services to help us improve the content and functionality of the Services to better understand our users and to improve the Services. The Company may use this information to contact you in the future to tell you about Services we believe will be of interest to you. If we do so, each marketing communication we send you will contain instructions permitting you to "opt out" of receiving future marketing communications. In addition, if at any time you wish not to receive any future marketing communications, or you wish to have your name deleted from our mailing lists, please contact us as indicated below.

If the Company intends on using any Personal Data in any manner that is not consistent with this Privacy Policy, the Company may, but is not obligated to, inform you of such anticipated use prior to or at the time at which the Personal Data is collected.

#### 3. _WE MAY SHARE YOUR PERSONAL DATA AND OTHER INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES_

Our Company is not in the business of selling your Personal Data. Maintaining the privacy of your Personal Data is a vital part of our relationship with you and an important aspect of the Services that we provide. There are, however, certain circumstances in which we may share your Personal Data with certain third parties without further notice to you, as set forth below:

  * Business Transfers. As we develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or assets, including Personal Data. In the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar event, Personal Data may be part of the transferred assets.
  * Agents, Consultants, and Third Parties. The Company, like many businesses, sometimes hires other companies to perform certain business-related functions. Examples of such functions include mailing information, maintaining databases, and processing payments. When we employ another entity to perform a function of this nature, we only provide them with the information that they need to perform their specific function. Additionally, we reserve the right to use third party analytics service providers and advertising partners to collect personally identifiable information about your online activities over time and across different websites when you use our Services, including details as described in this Privacy Policy. This Policy does not apply to - and we are not responsible for - those other parties and their use. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any third parties to learn about your choices about information they collect from you. Furthermore, we partner with third parties to provide certain support services to our users. These third parties are responsible for their own policies and procedures to protect your information. The Company is not responsible for the protection or use of information that users provide directly to any third party in conjunction with the use of Company's services. This privacy policy only applies to information provided directly to or obtained directly by Company during your use of our Services.
  * Legal Requirements. The Company may disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (i) comply with a legal obligation, (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of the Company, (iii) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Services or the public, or (iv) protect against legal liability.

#### 4. _HOW LONG WE KEEP YOUR CONTENT_

The Services enable you to transmit content in the form of Text, Pictures, Audio messages, and Video messages. Text and Pictures are stored on our servers for seven days, and then automatically deleted. Audio messages pass through our servers but are not stored. Video messages do not pass through our servers and are transmitted directly from user to user. Remember, however, that there are various ways that recipients of Content that you transmit can save your Content using any number of techniques: screenshots, third party software, or any other image-capture technology. It also is possible that someone might be able to access messages forensically or find them in a device’s temporary storage.

Although our systems are designed to delete Content automatically after a given period of time, we cannot promise that deletion will occur within a specific timeframe. Additionally, we may need to suspend those deletion practices if we receive valid legal process asking us to preserve Content or if we receive reports of abuse or other Terms of Service violations. Finally, we may also retain certain information in backup for a limited period of time if required by law.

#### 5. _CHILDREN SHOULD NOT SUBMIT PERSONAL DATA_

The Company does not knowingly collect Personal Data from individuals under the age of 18. If you are under the age of 18, please do not use the Services and do not submit any Personal Data through the Services. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children's internet usage and to help enforce our Privacy Policy by instructing their children under the age of 18 never to provide Personal Data to the Services. If you have reason to believe that someone under the age of 18 has provided Personal Data to the Company through the Services, please contact us at support@lovense.com, and we will endeavor to delete that information from our databases.

#### 6. _HOW WE SECURE YOUR INFORMATION AND CONTENT_

The Company takes commercially reasonable steps to protect the Personal Data provided via the Services from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. The Company uses security measures for any personal and account data that we store (emails, phone numbers, etc.). Account-identifiable or user-identifiable data collected through the Services may be encrypted and stored on our internal databases for up to seven (7) days. The Company will not sell or transfer account-identifiable data to third parties. Any accessible data associated with your account or your profile can be retrieved only if you provide us with your account identifier. Please be reminded, however, that no internet or email transmission or data storage is ever fully secure or error free and that information on the Services may be accessed, disclosed or altered. In particular, email sent to or from the Services may not be secure. Therefore, you should take special care in deciding what information you send to us. Please keep this in mind when disclosing any Personal Data to Company via the Internet.

Please note that all payments for products and services are processed by third-parties. The Company makes good-faith efforts to use third-party companies which employ proper protections for private information. However, we have no control over said companies; therefore, the Company exclusively disclaims any obligation or liability for said third-parties' processes and security measures.

#### 7. _CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS_

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 entitles California customers to request information concerning whether a business has disclosed personal information to any third parties for the third parties' direct marketing purposes. California customers who wish to request further information about our compliance with this law or have questions or concerns about our privacy practices and policies may contact us, in writing, at:

Hytto Ltd.

12/F AT Tower

No 180 Electric Rd.

North Point, Hong Kong

#### 8. _YOUR ABILITY TO MODIFY OUR USE OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA_

Under the GDPR, you have the following rights related to the Company’s use of your Personal Data.

Right to withdraw consent. You have the right to notify the Company that you no longer want them to process or use your Personal Data. You can do that by contacting the Company at [app@lovense.com](mailto:app@lovense.com) or the mailing address listed above in Section 7.

Right to data portability. You have the right to obtain a copy of your Personal Data stored and processed by the Company and direct the Company to transfer your Personal Data to another controller via CSV format. You can do that by contacting the Company at app@lovense.com or the mailing address listed above in Section 7.

Right to erasure/Right to be forgotten. You have the right to request that any of your Personal Data being stored or processed by the Company is deleted from our records. However, while we can delete your Personal Data from our current records, copies of your data may be stored in the Company’s inactive and archived records and will be deleted in accordance with the Company’s then-current document management policy. In some cases, your Personal Data may be continued to be stored in archived records of transactions or activities where Owner is required by law to retain such records.

Right to restriction of processing. You may request that the Company restrict the processing of your Personal Data. In such case, this may affect your ability to use or navigate the Services.

To exercise any of your rights above, please contact the Company at app@lovense.com or the mailing address listed above in Section 7. If you choose to exercise any of your rights listed above, it may affect your ability to use the Services, as the operation and functionalities provided on the Services may require the use of your Personal Data.

#### 9. _ABILITY TO REVIEW AND EDIT YOUR INFORMATION_

You may review and approve the Information about you that was stored in our database and obtained through your use of the Services. Upon your written request, we will remove that information from our database or change or correct Personal Data that you state is erroneous within applicable regulatory or other legal requirements. You should understand, however, that information about you in our database might come from a number of sources, so any inaccuracy is not necessarily the fault of the Company.

#### 10. _CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY_

The Company hereby reserves it right to modify/amend or otherwise change this Privacy Policy, as it deems necessary or appropriate because of legal compliance requirements or changes in Company's business practices. If you have provided us with an email address, we will endeavor to notify you, by email to that address, of any material change to how we will use personally identifiable information. If you do not agree with our updated Privacy Policy, please do not use our Services.

#### 11. _CONTACT US_

If you have any further questions about this Policy, please contact us by email at [app@lovense.com](mailto:app@lovense.com).
